JANE RATHER

Seasoned companion caregiver with seven consecutive years of in-home caregiving experience. Personable, patient professional who helps elderly and disabled residents fulfill their daily needsand benefit from social interaction. Extensive experience with elderly recovering from physical injuries.

123 Your Street, Greenwich, CT 12345 yo u remai I @exa m p I e.com (987) 654-3210

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMPANION CAREGIVER

Bright Light Home Health Care, Greenwich, CT

- June 2017- Present

Provide companionship to clients to increase their overall sense of well-being

- Engage clients in conversation and gentle activities such as walksand puzzles
- Perform light housekeeping tasks such as dusting, vacuuming, and changing bedding
- Run errands for clients as needed
- Communicate with clients' families and care teams
- Report environmental issues to supervisor

COMPANION CAREGIVER

White Oak Health Services, Stamford, CT

September 2014 - June 2017

- M a i ntained c lea n, safe, welcom i n g envi ron ments for c I i ents
- Organized clients¹ medications for safe, easy access
- Prepared meals for clients and kept kitchen area clean
- Listened to clients' needs and preferences and provided companionship
- Accompanied clients to doctors' appointments and other appointments when necessary
- Followed care plan, safety regulations, and company protocols at all times

EDUCATION

Prior coursework in anatomy, psychology, human development, and gerontology

KEY SKILLS

- Compassionate and personable
- Scheduling and organization
- Housekeeping
- Meal preparation
- Skilled communicator
- Discreet and trustworthy
- Care plan adherence

CERTIFICATIONS

- ◆ CPRcertification, 2014 to present
- First aid certification, 2014 to present